{
  "math":[
    {
      "id":1,
      "question":"36  ÷ 6 - 16  ÷ 8",
      "answer":"4",
      "step":"STEP BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":2,
      "question":"3  × 20  ÷ 5",
      "answer":"12",
      "step":"2 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":3,
      "question":"75 /100 = x/ 400",
      "answer":"300",
      "step":"2 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":4,
      "question":"___ × 10 = 8900",
      "answer":"890",
      "step":"3 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":5,
      "question":"Compare 2/ 6  3/6",
      "answer":"2/6 < 3/6",
      "step":"STAND HERE UNTIL YOU SOLVE"
    },
    {
      "id":6,
      "question":"Compare 1/5  1/2",
      "answer":"1/5 < 1/2",
      "step":"STAND HERE UNTIL YOU SOLVE"
    },
    {
      "id":7,
      "question":"18/20 = 90/x",
      "answer":"100",
      "step":"2 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":8,
      "question":"_____ × 98 = 98000",
      "answer":"1000",
      "step": "STAND HERE UNTIL YOU SOLVE"
    },
    {
      "id":9,
      "question":"1000 × __ = 682000",
      "answer":"682",
      "step": "3 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":10,
      "question":"∠EFH  = 120 deg ∠HFG = 30 deg ∠EFG = ?",
      "answer":"150 deg",
      "step": "GO TO START"
    },
    {
      "id":11,
      "question":"Simplify 15 : 24",
      "answer":"5/8",
      "step": "JAIL NO TURN TWICE"
    },
    {
      "id":12,
      "question":"11 = p + 1",
      "answer":"10",
      "step": "2 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":13,
      "question":"8 = z /6",
      "answer":"48",
      "step": "GO TO START"
    },
    {
      "id":14,
      "question":"8 + 2 (7 + 6)",
      "answer":"34",
      "step": "1 STEP BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":15,
      "question":"8  × 2 - 3  × 4",
      "answer":"4",
      "step": "5 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":16,
      "question":"6 + (8 + 5)",
      "answer":"19",
      "step": "STAND HERE UNTIL YOU SOLVE"
    },
    {
      "id":17,
      "question":"2  × 15  ÷ 3",
      "answer":"10",
      "step": "GO TO START"
    },
    {
      "id":18,
      "question":"(3 + 5)  × (9 - 9)",
      "answer":"0",
      "step": "2 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":19,
      "question":"b – 11 = 11",
      "answer":"22",
      "step": "3 STEPS BACK"
    },
    {
      "id":20,
      "question":"8 × ____ = 5600",
      "answer":"700",
      "step": "STAND HERE UNTIL YOU SOLVE"
    }
  ]
}